ILGWU Political Department Records 5780/103
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Western States Region, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 64)
- Orders for Subscription Lists and Receipt Books (Box 41, Folder 65)
- Campaign Committee Reports, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 66)
- Congressional Reports, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 67)
- Congressional Reports, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 68)
- Congressional Reports, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 69)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses (Box 41, Folder 70)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Washington Apartment, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 71)
- AFL-CIO News Bulk Subscriptions, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Garment Center Rally, 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Legislative/Political Conference, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- ILGWU National Legislative Conference, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  January 30-February1
- Campaign Committee, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Citizens Union, 1972-1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Common Cause, 1972-1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Congressional District Committees, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Cope Memos, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Election Administration Reports, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Empire State Report, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Federal Election Commission, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Justice, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Cope and AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Reapportionment News, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Justice Papers, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Cope, 1972-1982 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- 37th ILGWU Convention, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Political "Check-Off", 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Industrial Homework, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Letters to Chaikin, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Lobby Reporter (Political Finance), 1981-1983 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Memos to President Chaikin, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Memo for Staff Only, 1981-1983 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Memos to Staff, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Memos, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Reapportionment and Redistricting, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- State and Local Funds - Requests and Payments, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Requests to President Chaikin, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Youth Subminimum Wage, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Cuomo Campaign Material, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Congress, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Summary Annual Report for ILGWU Staff Retirement Plan, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- ILGWU National Legislative Conference, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Population of New York State by Counties, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Location of ILGWU Locals by State and Congressional District, 1980-1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Holiday, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  May, Volume 33 Number 5
- The New Leader, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous - Humphrey vs Nixon, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Memos, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Practical Politics, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  Volume I, Number I
- Viewpoint, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  Volume 8, Number 2
- Catalog of Films, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Hanover, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- National Journal, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  Number 36
- Newsweek, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  May 9
- State Legislature, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  January-March
- Empire State Report, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  December
- Politics and the Garment Worker Part 1, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Challenge, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Liberal Digest, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  Twenty First Anniversary
- Liberal Digest, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  Twentieth Anniversary
- Louisiana Story, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- New York City Central Labor Council AFL-CIO Trade Union Handbook, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- New York Affairs, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  Volume 4 Number 4 and Volume 5 Number 1
- Towards a More Perfect Union, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  The Platform of the Democratic Party